Guide to the Jewish Community Council of Greater Washington records, 1937-1988 MS2012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Committees, task torces, and working groups, 1941-1983; MS2012 Series 2; 22.5 Linear feet
  - Bicentennial Commission: Bicentennial Symposium, 1976 November 06-07 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Bicentennial Symposium, 1976 November 06-07 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Bicentennial Symposium, 1976 November 06-07 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Bicentennial Symposium, 1976 November 06-07 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Bicentennial Symposium, 1976 November 06-07 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Bicentennial Symposium, 1976 November 06-07 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Bicentennial Symposium, 1976 November 06-07 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Bicentennial Commission: American Jewish Committee - Programming for the Bicentennial, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Bicentennial Commission: American Jewish Music - A Bicentennial Celebration, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Articles and Addresses on the American Jewish Experience, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Bicentennial Commission: B'nai B'rith Bicentennial Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Board of Jewish Education Reporter - "Salute to America,", 1975 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Council of Jewish Federations and Welfare Funds - Council Reports, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Jewish Bicentennial Conferences, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Bicentennial Commission: National Jewish Welfare Board, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Bicentennial Commission: "Portal to America" - Program and Exhibition, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Community Task Force - Memos, Reports, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Community Task Force - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1974 January (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Community Task Force - Memos, Correspondence, 1974 February-December (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Community Task Force - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Community Task Force - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1977 January-May (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Community Task Force - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1977 June-December (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Community Task Force - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1978 January-June (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Community Task Force - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1978 July-December (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Community Task Force - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Community Task Force - Clergy Committee, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Community Task Force - Clergy Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Community Task Force - Clergy Committee, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Community Task Force - Economic Affairs Committee, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Community Task Force - Economic Affairs Committee, 1976 January-July (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Community Task Force - Economic Affairs Committee, 1976 August-December (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Community Task Force - Economic Affairs Committee, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Community Task Force - Media Committee, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Community Task Force - Media Committee, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Community Task Force - Media Committee, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Community Task Force - Media Committee, 1977 January-April (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Community Task Force - Media Committee, 1977 May-July (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Community Task Force - Media Committee, 1977 August-December (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Holocaust Committee Records, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Holocaust Committee Records, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Holocaust Committee Records, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Holocaust Committee Records, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Holocaust Committee Records, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Holocaust Committee Records, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yad Vashem Sub-Committee, 1975-1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yad Vashem - A Page of Testimony, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1973 April 29 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1974 April 21 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1975 April 06 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1975 April 06 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1976 April 25 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1976 April 25 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1977 April 17 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1977 April 17 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1978 April 30 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1978 April 30 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1979 April 22 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1979 April 22 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Holocaust Committee: Yom Hashoah - Holocaust Memorial Day, 1979 April 22 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Holocaust Committee: Background Materials - Holocaust Studies in the Public Schools, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Holocaust Committee: Background Materials - Holocaust Studies in the Public Schools, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Holocaust Committee: NBC Docu-Drama "Holocaust,", 1978 April 16-19 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Holocaust Committee: NBC Docu-Drama "Holocaust,", 1978 April 16-19 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Holocaust Committee: NBC Docu-Drama "Holocaust" Clippings, 1978 April 16-19 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Holocaust Committee: NBC Docu-Drama "Holocaust" - Study Guides, 1978 April 16-19 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Holocaust Committee: National Archives Holocaust Exhibit, 1978 May-September (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Holocaust Committee: Interfaith Dialogue - "Some Reflections and Implications on the Holocaust,", 1978 September 13 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Holocaust Committee: International Theological Symposium on the Holocaust, 1978 October (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Holocaust Committee: Proposed Symposium on the Holocaust, 1978 November (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Holocaust Committee: President's Commission on the Holocaust, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Holocaust Committee: President's Commission on the Holocaust, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Holocaust Committee: President's Commission on the Holocaust, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Holocaust Committee: President's Commission on the Holocaust, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Holocaust Committee: Raoul Wallenberg Candlelight Vigil, 1982 October 06 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Holocaust Committee: Vanessa Redgrave "Playing for Time" Controversy, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Holocaust Committee: Application for German War Reparations, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Holocaust Committee: World Gathering of Jewish Holocaust Survivors, 1981 June 15-18 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Holocaust Committee: World Gathering of Jewish Holocaust Survivors, 1981 June 15-18 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Holocaust Committee: American Gathering of Jewish Holocaust Survivors, 1983 April 11-14 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Holocaust Committee: American Gathering of Jewish Holocaust Survivors, 1983 April 11-14 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Holocaust Committee: American Gathering of Jewish Holocaust Survivors, 1983 April 11-14 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Minutes, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Minutes, Reports, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Minutes, Reports, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Memos, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR) - JCCGW Speaker Request Forms, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Desegregation of Washington Public Schools, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Desegregation: Busing - Background Materials, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Desegregation - Montgomery County Public Schools Conference, 1975 December 10 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Desegregation - Busing in Montgomery County, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Desegregation - Montgomery County Schools Desegregation, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Desegregation - Quality Integrated Education, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Gideon Bible Distribution in the Public Schools, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Gideon Bible Distribution in the Public Schools, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Gideon Bible Distribution in the Public Schools, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Gideon Bible Distribution in the Public Schools, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Gideon Bible Distribution in the Public Schools, 1956-1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Gideon Bible Distribution in the Public Schools, 1978-1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Conference - "The Jewish Student in the Public Schools,", 1975 October 19 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Northern Virginia Conference - "The Jewish Student in the Public Schools,", 1978 November 12 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - General, 1963-1965 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - Virginia State Aid to Parochial Schools, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - Maryland Commission on State Aid to Nonpublic Education, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - MD Commission on State Aid to Nonpublic Education, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - MD Commission, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - MD Commission, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - MD Commission, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - Maryland Parochiaid Referendum, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - Maryland Referendum, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - General, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - Maryland Referendum, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - Maryland Referendum, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiaid (Parochial Education) - Maryland Referendum, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiad (Parochial Education) - Maryland Legislation, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiad (Parochial Education) - General, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiad (Parochial Education) - Sage vs. Pearl, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochiad (Parochial Education) - Maryland County Transportation of Private School Students on Public School Buses, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Parochial (Parochial Education) - Maryland County Transportation of Private School Students on Public School Buses, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Calendars and Jewish Holidays, 1971-1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays - School Complaint Forms, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays - School Complaint Forms, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays - Stein vs. Fairfax County School Board, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays - Stein vs. Fairfax County School Board, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays - Stein vs. Fairfax County School Board, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays - Stein vs. Fairfax County School Board Legal Briefs, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays - Stein vs. Fairfax County School Board Legal Briefs, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Public School Scheduling Conflicts with Jewish Holidays, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Release Time for Religious Education, 1941-1945 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Release Time for Religious Education - McCollum Case, 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Release Time for Religious Education, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Release Time for Religious Education, 1950-1952 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Release Time for Religious Education, 1953-1958 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Release Time for Religious Education, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religion in the Public Schools - General, 1944-1946 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religion in the Public Schools - General, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religion in the Public Schools - General, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religion in the Public Schools - General, 1950-1958 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religion in the Public Schools - General, 1961-1967 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religion in the Public Schools - General, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religions and Ethnic Studies in the Public Schools, 1967-1969 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religions and Ethnic Studies in the Public Schools - Institute on Teaching About Religion in Education, 1969 April 11 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religions and Ethnic Studies in the Public Schools - Jewish and Hebrew Studies, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious and Ethnic Studies in the Public Schools - Jewish Studies, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious and Ethnic Studies in the Public Schools - Ethnic Heritage Studies Program, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious and Ethnic Studies in the Public Schools - Montgomery County Public Schools Multiethnic Convention, 1979 August 29-30 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious and Ethnic Studies in the Public Schools - Public Schools Ethnic Groups in American Society, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious and Ethnic Studies in the Public Schools - Montgomery County Public Schools Newsletters, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious and Ethnic Studies in the Public Schools - Black Experience and Culture Course for Montgomery County Public Schools, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious and Ethnic Studies in the Public Schools - Black Experience and Culture Course for Montgomery County Public Schools, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious and Ethnic Studies in the Public Schools - Reports on Black Experience and Culture Course, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools - Questionnaire, 1949-1950 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1953-1954 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1962-1964 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools - Hostile Responses to New Christian Guidelines, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Montgomery County Public Schools Religious Holiday Observance Workshop, 1975 September 18 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Revision of JCCGW Guidelines on Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools - School Complaint Forms, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools - School Complaint Forms, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools - School Complaint Forms, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools - School Complaint Forms, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): "Religious Holidays Observance in the Public Schools - No Easy Answers,", 1978 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holidays Observance in the Public Schools, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools - Florey vs. Sioux Falls School District, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Programs in the Public Schools (misc.), 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Baccalaureate Services in the Public Schools, 1950-1966 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Bible Reading and Prayer in the Public Schools, 1950-1956 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Bible Reading and Prayer in the Public Schools, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Court Cases, Schempp and Murray Decisions, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - H.B. 80 on Street Meditation, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Becker Amendment on School Prayer, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 1)